{
	"userAnswer": [
		[
			"integer",
			"stdfhdfh"
		],
		[
			"Integer",
			"fdhdf"
		],
		[
			"Integer",
			"dfhdf"
		],
		[
			"Integer",
			"dfhdf"
		],
		[
			"Float",
			"dfhdf"
		]
	],
	"questions": [
		[
			{
				"answer": "4",
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"correct": "Correct! Integers drop the decimal value.",
					"incorrect": [
						"Not quite. Do you remember how integers handle decimal values?"
					]
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "fillBlank"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Float",
				"choices": [
					"Integer",
					"Float"
				],
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"Float": "Correct! Operations involving decimals result in floating point numbers.",
					"Integer": "Not quite! Try breaking this expression into parts and solve each part."
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "multipleChoice"
			}
		],
		[
			{
				"answer": "float",
				"choices": [
					"integer",
					"float"
				],
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"float": "Correct! Any operation that involves a float will result in a float as output.",
					"integer": "Not quite! Think back to the lesson on what happens to calculations involving a float"
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "multipleChoice"
			},
			{
				"answer": "3.0",
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"correct": "Correct! Operations involving decimals result in floats",
					"incorrect": [
						"Notice that we're dividing by a float",
						"Do operations involving floats result in integers?"
					]
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "fillBlank"
			}
		],
		[
			{
				"answer": "7.0",
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"correct": "Correct! Any operation that involves a float will result in a float as output.",
					"incorrect": [
						"Not quite. Think back to the lesson on calculations with float",
						"Do operations that involve float ever result in integers?"
					]
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "fillBlank"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Integer",
				"choices": [
					"Integer",
					"Float"
				],
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"Float": "Not quite! This calculation does not involve any floats.",
					"Integer": "Correct! If a variable is a number, we can use it in arithmetic operations. In this case, it results in an integer"
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "multipleChoice"
			}
		],
		[
			{
				"answer": "8",
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"correct": "Correct! Since there are no decimals involved in the calculation, this results in an integer.",
					"incorrect": [
						"Remember, there are no decimals involved in this calculation.",
						"You can use variables in arithmetic operations. Try replacing, my_value with 4. What does that result?"
					]
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "fillBlank"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Float",
				"choices": [
					"Integer",
					"Float"
				],
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"Float": "Correct!",
					"Integer": "Not quite! This calculation involves a float"
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "multipleChoice"
			}
		],
		[
			{
				"answer": "Integer",
				"choices": [
					"Integer",
					"Float"
				],
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"Float": "Not quite. Think back to the lesson on how integers handle decimal points.",
					"Integer": "Correct! Integers drop the decimal value."
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "multipleChoice"
			},
			{
				"answer": "2.1",
				"code": "",
				"difficulty": "0",
				"feedback": {
					"correct": "Correct!",
					"incorrect": [
						"Calculate the modulus before the addition operator."
					]
				},
				"followupPrompt": "",
				"hint": "placeholder",
				"prompt": "",
				"type": "fillBlank"
			}
		]
	]
}
